# Dhananjay Supe () Featured

A self-motivated software professional with 5+ years of experience in web development. Professional level Knowledge in Web technologies and MySql. Able to adapt to and succeed in diverse technologies



Current Designation: Software Developer Total Experience: 5 Year(s)

Current Company: Verve Digital Technology Pvt Ltd.

Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Pune

and environments.

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: software developer,software development,requirement gathering,application programming,application

management,requirement analysis,javascript,mysql,ajax,jquery,json,bootstrap,html5,php,core java

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

## **Summary**

5+ years of work experience as a PHP Developer.

Have worked on more than 10 projects to develop web applications and mobile apps.

Along with PHP, HTML, JS and CSS, hands on experience on JAVA and Android.

Have worked at client locations to provide demos and training for functionalities and admin panel.

## **Work Experience**

Verve Digital Technology Pvt Ltd. as Software Developer

May 2016 to Till Date

A self-motivated software professional with 5 years of experience in web development. Professional level Knowledge in Web technologies and MySql. Able to adapt to and succeed in diverse technologies and environments.

MyosPaz Technologies as Software Developer

May 2015 to Mar 2016

Software developer

Pearl Logic Systems Pvt. Ltd as Software Developer

Oct 2013 to Jan 2015

Software Developer

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from BD College of Engineering, Sevagram in 2012

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
Windows XP/7, Ubuntu, Linux				
MS-OFFICE				
CSS	3	2020	4 Year(s) 3 Month(s)	
JavaScript	5	2020	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
HTML	5	2020	5 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
PHP,	7.3	2020	5 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
Android,	9	2019	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
CORE JAVA	8	2019	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
JQUERY		2020	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
AJAX		2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Expert			
Marathi	Expert			

## **Projects**

Project Title: KhetIndia

Client: SELFMADE SOFTWARE Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Mar 2020 - Till Date Project Location: Pune Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Role: Programmer

Skill Used: PHP,HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery,MySQL

Project Details: Online shopping portal to purchase Grocery, Food etc., it is complete ecommerce solution for grocery, Food and any kind of store. It have complete website, android native customer application for play store, android native delivery boy application and power full admin panel to manage everything from on single backend.

Project Title: Vkanekt

Client: SELFMADE SOFTWARE

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Apr 2019 - Mar 2020 Project Location: Pune Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Role: Programmer Team Size: 5

Project Details: Online education portal. Vkanekt Video Chat is a standalone web application with video, audio, recording, screen sharing file transfer and whiteboard face-to-face communication channels and integrated chat.

Project Title: LOST & FOUND SYSTEM FOR KUMBH 2019- PRAYAGRAJ.

Client: UP Police

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jul 2018 - Apr 2019 Project Location: Prayagraj Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Team Size: 3 Role: Programmer

Project Details: The primary objective of this Project is to digitally register lost persons at multiple lost and found registration centers situated in the Mela area, which will help lost persons and their family/ friends to get reunited at the Lost and Found centers. Some features of this project as

Data Entry of Lost Persons Online / Offline & Provision of attachment of Photos/ images, & other details (such as name, attire, address, Aadhar, ration card number, mobile number etc.)

Automatic matching of missing Person data with those of found & manual Confirmation to improve accuracy

Capturing photo and uploading in real time to the web

Auto generated TV Announcement.

Information sharing through social media WhatsApp, Facebook

User is be able to access the application through web client and Mobile Client.

Public address announcements at all lost and found centers for enabling family/ friends to re-unite with the lost persons.

**Graphical Data Live Presentation** 

Live YouTube

Project Title: GSTGATE

Client: SELFMADE SOFTWARE Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jun 2018 - Jul 2019 Project Location: Pune Onsite / Offsite: Offsite Role: Programmer Team Size: 10

Project Details: A web based and offline application which is useful for creating and maintaining invoices and filing GST to

government Portal.

## **Affirmative Action**

### **Work Authorization**

Category: OBC - non-creamy Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time